Guide to the Emilie F. Miller papers, 1987-1991
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Task Force on Developmental Disabilities 12, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Task Force on Developmental Disabilities 13, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Task Force on Developmental Disabilities 14, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Task Force on Developmental Disabilities 15, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Task Force on Developmental Disabilities 1990 Report to Congress (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Senate Finance Committee 1, 1988-1991 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Senate Finance Committee 3, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Senate Finance Committee 2, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Senate Finance Committee 4, 1988-1989 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Special Education 1, 1990s (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Special Education 2, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Special Education 3, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Special Education 4, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Northern Virginia Delegation Presentation, 1991 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Special Education 5, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Special Education 6, circa 1988 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Special Education 7, March 23, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Surrogate Motherhood Study 1, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Surrogate Motherhood Study 2, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Surrogate Motherhood Study 3, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Surrogate Motherhood Study 4, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Surrogate Motherhood Study 5, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Surrogate Motherhood Study 6, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Land Use Study 1, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Land Use Study 2, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Land Use Study 3, 1990s (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Land Use Study 4, 1991 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Land Use Study 5, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Land Use Study 6, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Land Use Study 7, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Tree Study, 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - House Joint Resolution 113-Vehicles Powered by Clean Transportation Fuels 1, 1990-1992 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - House Joint Resolution 113-Vehicles Powered by Clean Transportation Fuels 2, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - House Joint Resolution 113-Vehicles Powered by Clean Transportation Fuels 3, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - House Joint Resolution 113-Vehicles Powered by Clean Transportation Fuels 4, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - House Joint Resolution 113-Vehicles Powered by Clean Transportation Fuels 5, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - House Joint Resolution 113-Vehicles Powered by Clean Transportation Fuels 6, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - House Joint Resolution 113-Vehicles Powered by Clean Transportation Fuels 7, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - House Joint Resolution 113-Vehicles Powered by Clean Transportation Fuels 8, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 52- Abuse in Facilities for the Mentally Disabled Report- '88 Carry Over, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Bills and Resolutions Control List, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Senate Bill 573- Board of Rehabilitative Services, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 37- Social Services- Carry Over from '88 1, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 37- Social Services- Carry Over from '88 2, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 37- Social Services- Carry Over from '88 3, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Senate Bill 527- Civic Penalties for Zoning Violations, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 123- Commending Fairfax County Council of the Arts, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 153- Commending Ray Volrath, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 49-Eliminate Exemption of Commercial Zone Motor Carrier, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Senate Bill 718- Emergency Absentee Ballot, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Senate Bill 715- Exceptions to Residential Landlord Act, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Senate Bill 714- Exceptions to Residential Landlord Tenant Act, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Senate Bill 596- Extended School Day Programs 1, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Senate Bill 596- Extended School Day Programs 2, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Senate Bill 571- Fairfax City Building and Fire Regulations, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 130- Incentives for Consolidating School Functions, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Senate Bill 719- In Person Absentee Ballot Deadline, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Senate Bill 535- Organizations Exempt from Property Tax- INOVA Services, Incorporated, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Senate Bill 597- Precluding Death Penalty for the Mentally Retarded 1, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Senate Bill 597- Precluding Death Penalty for the Mentally Retarded 2, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Senate Bill 597- Precluding Death Penalty for the Mentally Retarded 3, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - House Joint Resolution 164- Restroom Equity, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Senate Bill 598- Rights of Mental Patients, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Senate Bill 471- School Board Date of Appointment, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Senate Bill 572- School Capital Expenditure Financing, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Senate Bill 717- Selection for Jury Duty, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Senate Bill 64- Blake Lane, 1987-1989 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Senate Bill 65- Prorated Personal Property Taxes- Fairfax City, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Senate Resolution 37- Study on Impact of Social Security Taxes, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Senate Resolution 54- Doug Walker Commemorative, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Senate Bill 794- Subdivision and Site Plan, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Senate Bill 691- Taxes, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 152- Thomas Jefferson High School 1, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 152- Thomas Jefferson High School 2, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 152- Thomas Jefferson High School 3, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 152- Thomas Jefferson High School 4, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 138-Mental Health, Mental Retardation, and Substance Abuse, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Senate Bill 716- Violations by Landlords- Penalties, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Senate Bill 793- Virginia Alcohol Safety Action Program, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 151- Women's History Month, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Senate Resolution 45- Death of Maureen V. O'Donnell, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 109- Honoring George Snyder, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 101- Women's History Month in Virginia, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Senate Bill 63- Repeal of Advocacy Department for the Developmentally Disabled, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 50- Funding State Mental Health, Mental Retardation, and Substance Abuse Services- 6 year plan, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Senate Bill 243- Economic Development Authority- Commission Enlargement, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 52- Study of Criminal Prosecution of Persons who Abuse the Mentally Retarded, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Senate Bill 64- Blake Lane, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Senate Bill 129- Advertising by Licensed Facilities or Institutions for the Mentally Ill, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 22- Alternative Psychiatric and Drug Treatment Insurance Coverage, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Bills- for Other State Clearinghouses, 1986 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Bills Resolutions Tracking (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Budget Amendments, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Budget Amendment- Staffing Mental Retardation Training Center, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Chief Patron Report 1, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Chief Patron Report 2, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Chief Patron Report 3, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Senate Bill 301- Civil Penalties for Violations of Zoning Ordinances, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Co-patroned Bills 1, 1988 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Co-patroned Bills 2, 1988 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 44- Commending Astronaut Pierre Thuot, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Senate Bill 303- Definition of Cosmetology 1, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Senate Bill 303- Definition of Cosmetology 2, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Senate Bill 303- Definition of Cosmetology 3, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 121- Earth Day, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 119- Study- Family Support Services, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Senate Bill- Frank Crosby Local 26, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Graphic of Clearinghouse Growth, 1980s-1990s (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Senate Joint Resolution- James Weiss Jefferson Jeopardy Finalist, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Legislation- Public Facilities, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Mental Health Association of Northern Virginia- Board Members and Council Members, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Committee on Human Services, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - New Self-Help Groups, 1980s (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 148- Northern Virginia Youth Symphony Association, 1990s (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Senate Bill 139- Optometrists, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Senate Bill 302- Prescription of Drugs by Certain Practitioners, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Senate Bill 41- Property Tax Exemption, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Senate Bill 475-Extended Day Care 1, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Senate Bill 475- Extended Day Care 2, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Senate Bill 475- Extended Day Care 3, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Senate Bill 111-Regulation of Child Care Services Facilities, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Revised Proposal, 1980s-1990s (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Research and Statistics, New York, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Self-Help, circa 1990s (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - Self-Help Clearinghouse File- Mental Health Association of Northern Virginia, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 120- Self-Help Group Clearinghouse, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Senate Bill 210- Sentencing in Capital Murder Cases 1, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Senate Bill 210- Sentencing in Capital Murder Cases 2, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - Senate Bill 476- Sentencing Proceedings, Capital Cases 2-1, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Senate Bill 476- Sentencing Proceedings, Capital Cases 2-2, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - "Women in Politics" Center, 1989-1990 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Women in Military Service Memorial, 1989-1991 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 206- Alternative Fuels Pilot Projects, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Senate Bill 526- Association of Retarded Citizens Property Tax Exemption, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Senate Bill 669-Authority to Cut Grass Fairfax County, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - 1991 Chief Patron Report (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - City of Fairfax Parking Authority, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Commending Resolution 1, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Commending Resolution 2, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Commending Resolution 3, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Commending Resolution 4, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Senate Bill 668- Community Services Board Procurement Act Exemption, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 211- Commending Thomas Jefferson High School Merit Semifinalists, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Senate Bill 696- Cosmetology, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 122- Consolidating Licenses Functions within Health and Human Resources, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Senate Bill 820- Deemed Consent for HIV Testing, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Senate Bill 642- Election Returns and Procedures after Polls Close, 1990-1991 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Senate Bill 507- Exemption for Non-Profit Groups in Fairfax City, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Senate Bill 475- Extended Day Care 1, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Senate Bill 475- Extended Day Care 2, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Senate Bill 475- Extended Day Care 3, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Senate Bill 475- Extended Day Care 4, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Extended Day Care Bill Support File, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Information on 1991 Senate Bills and House Bills (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Senate Bill 695- Informed Consent (Peanut Bill II), 1991 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Senate Bill 542- Jewish Community Foundation Property Tax Exemption, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Legislation- 1990 Carryover (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Legislation Tracking Forms, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Legislative Services, 1990 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 208- March Music in Our Schools Month, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Senate Bill 641- Notice of Candidacy and Required Filings, 1990 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - House Bill 424- Peanut Bill I 1, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - House Bill 424- Peanut Bill I 2, 1990 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - House Bill 424- Peanut Bill I 3, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - House Bill 424- Peanut Bill I 4, 1990 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - House Bill 424- Peanut Bill I 5, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - House Bill 424- Peanut Bill 1 6, circa 1987 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Senate Bill 475- Extended Day Care- 5, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Senate Bill 543- Removal of Unsafe Vehicles- City of Fairfax, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 51- Study Regulating Marriage and Family Therapists, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Restoration of Private School Funding- Fairfax County, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Schedule Resolution, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Temporary Employment Agencies, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 247-Virginia Earth Day, April 21, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 216- Virginia Women's History Month, March 1991 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 200- Special Education 1, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 200- Special Education 2, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 200- Special Education 3, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 200- Special Education 4, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 200- Special Education 5, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 200- Special Education 6, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Senate Joint Resolution 200- Special Education 7, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Five Minute Tape, circa 1990 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Political Video Duplicators Example Video Cassette, 1991 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Campaign, 1988-1991 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Advertisements, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Campaign Literature- Other Candidates 1, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Campaign Literature- Other Candidates 2, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Campaign Literature- Other Candidates 3, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Materials 1, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Campaign Materials 2, 1980;s (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Materials 3, 1980s (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Campaign Materials 4, 1980s (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Campaign Prospectus- David Battaglia and Leslie Byrne, 1980s (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Campaign Staff, 1980s (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Candidates and Campaigns, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - City of Fairfax Future Land Use Plan, 1980s (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Democrat Newsletter, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Democratic Party of Virginia, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Editorials and Columns, 1980s (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Endorsements, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Issues, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Strategy, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Fundraising, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Fundraiser for Emilie Miller, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Georgette Klinger, Incorporated, March 13, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - John Milliken, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Joint Brochure and Other Literature, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Junior League of Virginia, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Kaiser Permanente- Phillip Marstiller, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Kennedy Library Foundation, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Kentucky Colonels, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - King's Dominion, March 1991 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - The League of Women Voters of Virginia General Assembly Directory, 1990-1991 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - General Assembly of Virginia Senate Members, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Virginia Legislative Directory, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Senate Joint Resolutions 48, 29, 59, 1980s-1990s (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Larry Larsen, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Lazaurus at the Gate, 1990s (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - League of Women Voters Mental Health Study, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Lee Highway, 1991 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Lee Highway-Perkins, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Lee Highway- Thompson Family Cemetery, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Legal Secretaries, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Lemon Law, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1980s (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Letters-Newly Registered Voters, March-August 1988 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Letter to Fairfax City- Newspaper Clippings, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Mailing List Systems, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Mantua Precinct Letters, 1991 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Metro Application, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Miller for Senate Campaign Budget (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Miller for State Fundraising Events, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Miller on the Issues, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Petitions, circa 1987 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Phone Book and Instruction Scripts, circa 1987 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Poll, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Pre-election Coverage, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Press Releases, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Questionnaires, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Republican Candidates, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Resume, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Return for Files Treasurer, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Recount, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Signs- Permit and Locations, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - The Firebird Ball, 1990 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - The Democrat Publication Campaign Kickoff, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Underdog Fund, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Senate, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Trial Lawyers Association, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Victory Group, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Virginian Pilot Poll, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Volunteer Booklet and Form, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Volunteer Lists, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Voter Statistics, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Volunteers- Students (Certificate) (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Women's Campaign Fund, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Women's National Democratic Club, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Abortion Rights (Campaign) (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Ads, 1980s (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - 1991 Campaign (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Campaign- Administrative, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - An Evening Honoring Two Great Senators (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Campaign Chronicle for the Friends of Miller, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Donations, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Campaign Materials 1, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Campaign Materials 2, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Campaign Materials 3, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Campaign Materials 4, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Campaign Materials 5, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Campaign Plan: Budget, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Campaign Response, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Candidacy for Re-election, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Candidate Filing Forms, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Mark Charette, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Choice Issues, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Citizens for Balanced Growth Political Action Committee, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - 1991 Correspondence- not answering (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Dental Hygienists' Association, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Door to Door Campaign, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Right to Education, 1990s (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Educators- Retired List and Letter, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Election Publications, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Emily's List, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Research- Committee on Local Government, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Research- Committee on General Laws, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Research- Committee on Education and Health, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Research- Committee on Rehabilitation and Social Services, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Emilie's Voting Record, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Endorsements, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Environment, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Fairfax City, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Fairfax County Democratic Committee, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Fairfax County Events, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Fairfax Medical Society Gala, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Finance- Miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - First Fund Raising Letter to Constituents, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Introductory Letter to New Precincts (Marshall and Lincolnia), 1991 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Letters 1, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Letters 2, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Mental Health, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Mothers and Majority Leaders, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Originals, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Other Surveys, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Petitions- Filled and Notarized, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Petitions- Original, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Polling Campaign, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Polling Places Information, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Press Clips and Letters, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Precinct Information, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Press Releases, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Questions or Surveys- to be Completed- Dated Materials, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Questionnaires 1, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Questionnaires 2, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Questionnaires 3, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Radio Appearance, October 23, 1987 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Statistical Data, 1991 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Volunteer Meetings, March 1991 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Voting Statistics, 1987-1991 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Women's Campaign Conference, 1991 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Women's Groups Lists, 1991 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Women's Fundraiser for Emilie Miller, 1991 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Coalition Community Services Board, 1992 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Coalition- Department for Rights of Virginians with Disabilities, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Case Management in Substance Abuse Treatment, 1992 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Coalition Steering Committee Meeting, 1992 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1992 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Mental Health, Mental Retardation, and Substance Abuse Services Final Bill Disposition, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Consortium for Citizens with Disabilities, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Special Education for Children with Disabilities in Virginia, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Coalition and Roster of Community Services Boards, 1992-1993 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Coalition- Virginia Board for People with Disabilities, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia- Miller Record, 1989-1991 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1990s (Box 81, Folder 15)